Good evening everyone. This is Casa, Ayame, and Catherine, who are progressing today.
Yay! Catherine!
You have to say "Katherine"!
Don't make a mess!
Is it okay if I say "Katherine"?
Kath isn't quite right.
I made a mistake. I'm sorry.
Yes, I'm sorry. Not today,
This is the 180th edition of Ukka's Delightful and Fabulous Showroom.
I would like to deliver this edition with a new subtitle.
I would like to decide on the subtitle here,
We will be delivering a program based on the subtitle,
We will be delivering the showroom under the original rules of Ukka.
There will be almost no materials.
I was wondering what the subtitle would be for this show,
But I was thinking about what to call this showroom,
We have the final day of our spring tour on April 16th,
Also, it will be our first showroom in the new fiscal year 2023,
I guess that's what I'm thinking about.
Fiscal year 2023.
Academic year.
Well then, let's go.
I am Rina Yuki, a new college sophomore.
I'm new.
Good.
Congratulations.
I'm Ruri Aoi, a new company employee, first year. Please.
I've climbed up to the adult dialogue.
I'm Aimi Kawase, first year new job hunter.
I see you've been job hunting.
I was wished to get a job at Starlast.
I'm currently job hunting. I'm at Starlast.
Was it dark?
It was dark. I'm still working part-time.
Part-time job?
It was a part-time job.
What are we going to do? Is there anything?
Oh, let's TOGETHER.
Catherine and Hal.
With Katherine. We don't have any Catherine people.
The acrylic board is gone!
We can do this!
A world line that can be touched.
What shall we do?
I want something fun.
Yes, that's right.
Fun.
Happy.
Yes, I like happy subtitles.
Yes, I do.
Oh, I think it's totally fine to commemorate the Nostoacril board.
Certainly.
It's that kind of time already.
Yes, it is.
That's the era we live in.
Ugkka will support your new life with a spring tour.
That's nice. It's a long time, but, you know.
I'll be there.
Like, happy, happy, happy high shins.
Like happy happy highsin.
Okay, let's make it a spring tour happy-happy-happy-high-shine.
I think it's easier to think of it if it's rough. And the corners.
Yes, it is.
Gentle.
I thought about it.
Okay, I'd like to do the Spring Tour Happy High Sin this time.
So, I will do the title code.
Ukka no,
Happy and Fuuna Showroom,
Spring Tour Happy Haisin!
Good evening everyone. We, Uka here.
As I mentioned earlier, today's new child is me, Mika Kawasawa.
Yay! I'm here!
Well, please introduce yourself.
My name is Ruri Aoi.
I'm a hero.
A hero?
My name is Rina Yuki.
Pleased to meet you.
So, today is the 180th.
That's great.
I didn't expect it to be so.
Thank you very much for watching the 180th edition of Ukka's Delightful and Fukuna Showroom.
Thank you very much.
I would like to take this opportunity to spread the word,
In order for as many people as possible to see this broadcast, we will be tweeting an announcement on Twitter from now on,
Please retweet the tweet.
Please retweet my tweet.
I'm going to pose for a picture, and you can tweet a screenshot of the comment I've received,
Today is Happy High Sin, so it's a fun pose.
It's a happy pose.
I'll leave it to you.
You all can do anything you want, like happy, happy camera.
Feel free to do whatever you want.
As long as it conveys the feeling that you're having fun, it's totally fine.
Write whatever you want.
It's free.
Let's be free. Today.
This is a happy pose.
I'm going to go with happy pose.
Then, please give us the Nomu-Nomu Leader Squasho.
Please do.
Okay, happy pose!
Okay, is that OK?
Yes!
Is it OK?
Thank you!
I feel like this is the screen of the delivery person.
The colors are brighter.
I'm going to go see what I can do with the outfit.
The one you can do in the editing section.
The kind of thing you can do in the photo section.
It's nice.
If you see an official tweet from Ukka, please tweet it to us.
Please tweet us.
Now, let's go to the free talk,
First of all, between the last time and this time, we had a spring tour on April 1,
First of all, between the last time I delivered the newsletter and this time, we had our spring tour in Osaka on April 1.
It had been a long time since we had been to Osaka, right?
It was the first time since summer, right?
After last summer?
Bibimbe?
It was the first time since then.
It was kind of hot, wasn't it?
It was really hot.
I don't know,
The city of Osaka in the Kansai region was so noisy,
Of course it was hot, but it was also hot,
But also because there was not much depth on the stage,
The lights were very close to us.
That's for sure.
So the light was very strong,
It was like direct sunlight.
So it was really hot,
It was the hottest.
Yes, it was. In the spring tour.
We were soaking wet.
It was so hot. I was like, "Why?
Why? I was so surprised.
That's because we sold out,
The place was packed with customers,
It was hot, wasn't it? As hot as we were.
That's for sure. The density.
That's right. By selling out.
It was hot.
That's tough.
But it felt like a live concert. It felt like a live house.
It was a good feeling.It was a good feeling.
I stayed in Osaka for a couple of nights, or rather, I stayed over afterwards,
I stayed over after the tour,
Were you able to go sightseeing?
Yes, we did.
Where did we go?
There.
I heard a little bit about it.
I've been wanting to go there for a while.
Oh, that's right.
Tell him it's up there.
Did you tell him?
Probably,
Have you ever been to Osaka for a re-leave or something?
I had only been to Osaka for reeves and such,
I've never been to Osaka for sightseeing or anything like that,
So I never really went to Osaka.
I always wanted to go there, even though it is a famous place,
I had always wanted to go there, and when I told Ruri about my dream,
When I told Ruri about my dream, she agreed.
I'm glad. She agreed to do it.
I'm so happy for you. In my heart, I was deeply moved.
Thank you.
Sorry, sorry.
I was able to eat Bakugyaki on the Shinkansen on the way home,
I was happy.
I went to eat Boku Boku.
We lined up, right?
You did?
I've lined up this video of us sightseeing,
I wonder if it will be posted somewhere later.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
I took some pictures, but I don't know what I did with them yet.
I didn't send it.
I don't know what happened because I didn't send it.
I'll let you know if I find a place where you can see it.
Also, it was really hot during the day.
I wonder if it is hot in Kansai.
It felt like summer.
It was like the sun was hot and there was no cold.
It rains a little too much. It always rains.
Was it Nagoya?
It was a very rainy season.
Nagoya.
And Fukuoka was also rainy.
Fukuoka? No, it was fine. It was sunny.
Was it sunny?
It was sunny. It was fine.
I'm so surprised. Can you film it?
That's why I was so happy that it was sunny.
It was so hot.
And it was raining on the trip.
Yes, it was.
The weather forecast called for rain for two days.
We really wanted to go to Universe, but we decided not to because of the rain.
It just cleared up.
It was like...? It was like that.
I would like to go to Kansai again.
I would like to go.
Please wait.
They are waiting.
I'm going to start cooking.
That's what I'm going to do.
Happy 20th birthday to Harina on April 9.
Thank you very much.
I turned 20.
I'm 20 years old.
I'm an adult.
What did you do for your birthday?
You can reveal your birthday in the action room,
Reveal?
I did a birthday party,
I had a lot of fun, and everyone celebrated with me,
It was a lot of fun,
It took longer than I thought it would.
The time.
I thought I made everyone lose sleep because of the time.
I looked at me for a second.
Really?
I saw it on Comodo.
It's all there.
At Comado.
I thought they were doing it.
But it was so fast.
The story and the live performance.
I made the story around 11:30,
And then I sent it to the manager line,
I would send it to the manager's line at 11:30, and ask him to confirm the update on Twitter.
I was on standby on the line, too.
The line was on standby,
Storyline in order.
Storyline.
That's great.
Most of the people came to the raise.
Really?
Raise came to me too.
That's why,
Ruiz was the first one to come.
She's really hot.
My time.
What?
You came?
Louise was the first to arrive,
Before that, we were all trying to guess
We were trying to guess who would be the first.
Ruiz was the third,
But she turned it around.
No way.
Ruiz-chan, Moa-chan, and Ayame-chan rule and ba-ba-ba-ba.
That's not coming, is it?
At first, we were on the edge.
The day before,
Already at Ruiz-kun's time,
The first.
I received it as an advance.
I said I was going to borrow it in advance.
So it was practically like, come to Raise.
I was happy.
I'm looking forward to it. That too.
That's right.
I'd be sad if they didn't come.
I'm a little ashamed of myself for waiting.
Like I'm going to be lonely.
That's nice.
How old are you, Louise, when you're waiting?
Eighteen.
I'll be 19 next.
I'll be 19 this year.
Still young.
I'm going to make her wait two more years. Until I can drink.
Moa-chan is not ready yet.
Take your time.
Do you want me to buy you a drink?
I'll drink first.
Can you leave me here?
I'll find you something nice.
Nice place, good taste.
Forgive me.
I'm an adult.
Like this.
I think I got a lot of comments from a lot of people.
I think I received comments from a lot of people.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
I guess that's about it.
That's all.
Is that all?
Yes. I'll go to the corner.
Okay.Yes.
Title Call.
Spring Tour Happy High Scene.
That's why.
So.
The first one.
Happy Ai ya Osakuma.
The three of us will sakk love with a three-letter word.
The second person says something unhappy.
The third person should say something super happy.
Like negative-negative-positive.
And it's three words.
Three letters.
Like "apple" or something like that?
When the subject comes up, it starts with "Ri".
I see.
So you want me to get it.
That's difficult.
A three-letter word.
Please give it to me.
What is a three-letter word?
It's pretty hard to find 3 letters.
It's difficult for everyone.
What's the difference between a small one in the middle and a big one in the middle?
Like a cup.
Like Toppo.
Ayame.
Who should we start with?
Do you want to finish? Inside Ayame.
I'll start with a super happy feeling.
Okay, I'll go first.
Ready! Ayame's...
Oh, I lost my wallet.
Ayame's, no!
I don't know where I dropped it.
Is that what you mean?
Then, let's just keep going with 1, 2, and 3, shall we?
Like a connection.
Yes. Oh, I lost my wallet.
Oh no. I don't know where I dropped it.
I found it at Mercurogawa. Super happy!
Yay!
Thank God! I found it!
I was at Mercklogow for cherry blossom viewing.
Oh, yeah?
I was at the Hanami at the Mercurogawa.
Just a hunch.
Mercklogawa?
Mercklogawa.
Mercklogawa. Mercklogawa.
Super happy!
Well, that's how it is, isn't it?
After the first one, the second one was close to that.
Say the words that connect,
I see.
Rustle it out.
After saying the third letter,
I'll say this rusty word,
"Aa~irokko~.
Great! That's so good!
That's great!
I'll find the rust.
Yes, please.
So happy!
There's a lot of good stuff here.
Tanuki.
It's funny.
Iniku is four letters.
That's true.
It would be interesting if they were all written in kanji.
It's not like this is meat or anything.
Let's find a theme.
What do you have?
Happy face.
Apollo!
Apollo's good!
Let's try it the other way around.
Okay, well, Rina-chan should be super happy,
I think it's good for you.
I'll go for the red one.
Rainy days really bring down the tension.
My hair in a polo.
I have a long vacation, so let's go!
Mind you, it's a one-man song now.
It's wonderful!
I don't know, I'm starting to feel happy
I'm starting to feel happy.
That's a lot of positivity in your life.
That, I feel like I can make everything positive.
That's already maboros.
Because if it's a rag, it's hair.
Ragging!
It's falling off.
I mean, it's falling to pieces.
It's falling out.
Next time, we'll probably have to tighten three strands.
Riru will be next.
Cherry blossoms are nice.
Seasonal, too.
Okay, then.
First, then three.
Okay.
Yes, please.
One, two, three.
I'm sorry.
I fell down from the top of the hill.
Ugh!
I hurt my knee!
Thank goodness I'm in running shoes!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Great. I'm having fun. I want to do more.
Good thing I'm in running shoes.
What?
Good thing you're in running shoes.
I'm so tall, I fell down.
I felt good! Like that.
I'm glad I'm in running shoes! I was like, "I'm glad I'm in running shoes!
What?
I fell down.
I fell down in my running shoes.
If I had been in heels or something, I would have had a bigger injury.
So, you're making it a little bit easier.
Like a successful landing.
I didn't land, but it's like this.
Let's go around again.
One more lap?
Let's see.
What would you like?
Three letters.
Three letters are hard.
I don't know.
That's good.
Tuna?
Tuna looks difficult.
I'll be number 3. I'll go with 1, 2, and 3.
I'll start from here.
From me?
Mom scolded me!
She smeared my messed up toys!
Ron...daddy longyala is sad too, but it looks like I made it, so I'll take it!
Longyearapa...
Introduce me at ICAO.
ahahahahaha!
I want a blunt daddy!
milligrams
A little past the waveA Little Wave Past
????
Oh yeah...
I was thinking of Leo before that....
Hmmm...
Happy 10 where if you're a woman, you're a c-junkie.
boo baas, I hope you'll do whatever it takes.
I want you to do it no matter what...
I'm sure it's not like that at all...
I mean...
3 sentences, right?
No. 2, No. 2, from my mouth...
We're out of grape juice!
They're out of grape juice!
Good night...
I'm stronger than a lion now!
Yeah!
Stronger than a lion!
What's so hard?
I couldn't come up with anything.
Everyone is saying "yay".
It has a cute emoji on it. They're saying "yay.
There are hearts and stuff. Thanks.
Yay! Yay!
Yay! Everyone is happy.
Well, here's the thing.
It's perfect.
Yes, it is.
Last one.
Okay.
Let's see what we got.
Lastly, do you want to go with "Utsuka"?
Utsuka?
Utsuka, then number 1.
Yes, number 2.
I couldn't become Ultraman.
Well, I'm looking forward to next week's Doraemon, but I'm not looking forward to it.
The camera is watching me. I'm so happy!
What do you mean?
I'm glad I came.
I'm still positive.
Yeah, so I'm not just having fun.
I'm sorry I was rude to Doraemon.
Doraemon might not get the job.
He won't come anymore.
He's not coming.
Oh, no!
It's here.
That was fun!
It's over.
That was fun.
But it's nice to be happy, isn't it? I'm so excited!
The weather was a bit of a bummer today, so I was a bit nervous, but now I'm a little more excited.
I'm so excited.
Posic!
Thank you, Mr. Takahashi!
Posyck.
Happy spring!
Happy Spring! Spring means Cherry Blossom Viewing!
For those of you who are not happy because it's raining or you've been busy or whatever, let's go see cherry blossoms with Uka!
The three of us will draw a picture of cherry blossoms, so please look at it and enjoy the cherry blossoms!
I did it! My favorite time of the day is when I draw!
What?
Mmm-hmm.
You didn't know?
Are you painting?
I paint, I paint.
On a daily basis.
Everyday.
Yes, I do.
On duct tape, on the floor...
When there's duct tape on the floor...
I'm sure...
I draw on it.
That's right.
I like drawing, but this...
There's only one sking.
Ours.
Oh, I see.
You're missing a color... from earlier.
Yes, I see.
You think.
Well, I'll start with this one.
Oh, I'll go from my favorite.
All right.
Let's put in today's cherry blossoms.
There are many kinds of cherry blossoms.
Of course there are.
Oh, pink.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much.
I used to draw cherry blossoms a lot.
Maybe...
Maybe.
I saw it for the first time when I introduced myself.
In April?
They give you a piece of paper to introduce yourself.
We wrote our introductions on it, and when we drew...
I drew cherry blossoms.
I don't know anything about that.
You don't know?
No, I don't know.
I don't know. It's a little bit...
Maybe it's local. That's...
It's local.
It's pretty nice, though.
Good night.
What do you think?
Why don't you want it?
Is it done?
It's done.
Yes, sir.
One at a time.
Then, please.
Then! Cherry blossoms.
Oh!
They're all gone.
I knew there was something like that,
The wind and all that.
It's a nice touch.
Yes, it is. Then, Ryu-chan, please come in.
This is a cherry tree.
Is this the cherry tree?
This way.
We decided to use cherry blossoms as the main flower.
If you zoom in, it looks like this.
Only cherry blossoms.
Okay.
Here it is. Cherry blossoms.
Oh! Beautiful.
I changed it to putty.
Patties.
This is a sea of cherry blossoms.
Aah!
Squishy time.
It's scrub time.
Yes, sir.
So, then, hanami.
Ohanami.
We're watching by ourselves.
Like this.
Like a fair.Like a fair.
It's a fair.
Well, this spring, Yuri got her heart broken.
That happened, didn't it?
What happened? After that.
It was hard to see her face.
That's right.
That's not a good image.
That's a picture.
I'll forget about it.
But Rina got married.
That's right.
I'm sorry, Rina.
I didn't tell you.
You didn't?
You didn't tell her?
I was betrayed by my friends.
Every one.
My friends betrayed me.
Why is the music over?
I'm now a fish.
I'm now a fisherman.
When I get married, I want to get married in the spring. Because my birthday is in the spring.
I see.
So when I thought spring-like music would be nice...
Mr. Uogami.
I looked for it on Music Miss.
So it's Music Miss.
Uogami.
So I thought of the Uogami style.
That's right.
It's a marriage.
I've reached my limit.
That's nice. Rina-chan.
You're my dream guy.
I'll do my best.
But, Ayabi-chan, I heard you got certified recently too.
That's right.
Because it's spring.
During cherry blossom perfume.
As expected.
So cool.
Marry me with Yuukyan.
Yuukyan.
Yuukyan?
I brought you dinner, didn't I?
Yes, I did. Today.
Keep it.
Because we're going to see cherry blossoms.
I brought it.
You brought yellow, right?
Can I start?
I thought fried food is good for cherry-blossom viewing.
Karaage?
I made fried tuna.
Homey!
Uri-chan bought strawberries!
Oh, wow!
What kind are they?
They are long and thin.
It's a thin and slender strawberry.
Thin and fine strawberries!
Oh, they are the kind that are eaten.
They are rare nowadays.
There's also the ballet and so on.
That's fine too.
Cute!
What did you bring, Hina-chan?
Fish sauce!
I wanted to make an ASCII version of "fish is a housewife".
I knew it!
You're newlyweds!
Colorful pasta!
Cute!
Isn't she cute?
Actually, I still feel like a girl.
Yes, it is.
Housewives are different here, aren't they?
They start from the south.
From me.
That's right.
Let's eat then.
Bon appétit.
Thank you all so much.
It looks a little hard to eat strawberries.
No, it's not.
It's colorful pasta with fish sauce, right?
We're going to open a restaurant soon.
A cafe!
He seems pretty confident about it.
Try it, it's delicious.
Okay, bye.
What about me?
Is it good?
Bon appétit.
It's just for looks.
Uri, no. I wanted to be rude. That's not what I meant.
So excuse me.
Right up to the spot.
So, let's leave early.
Thank you. Everyone, today.
Certainly.
Let's all go see cherry blossoms together.
Don't make a dirty person. What is it?
Eat. Eat.
This way. Please eat, too.
Hanami for 3 people.
Yay.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
So, gradually happy game!
Yay!
Be sure to say something happier than the person in front of you and cause a happy flu!
What are you doing already?
I'm feeling good today.
I think it's this one over here.
Want to give it a try?
There's a game you can play where you get more and more excited.
Ahhh...
OK, let's start with something not so happy.
A little story?
Say something about writing.
Everyone's.
I'll go first. Let's go around in order.
My hair is a little brighter now that I've had it roached.
I'm so happy to be able to buy the new gummies.
That was fast.
Let's do it again. Let's do it again.
Too soon.
Not yet.
Still a problem? Maybe.
You got happy too soon.
I was still in the negative.
Oh, I see.
A little more negative.
The color has faded.
You're not happy. Not really.
It would have been better if I hadn't bought it.
That's right. On the contrary.
You couldn't buy it?
I couldn't.
The gummy bears.
That's right.
I couldn't buy them.
They came from inside.
Oh, I'm Pikani.
Yes.Yes, I have a problem with my hair color.
My hair color is fading and getting lighter.
I found some new gummies, but I couldn't buy them because I didn't have enough money.
Yay! Make it all yourself!
This water tastes so good today.
The camera seems to leak a lot today.
I feel like shiba-mi.
I think the lipstick Ma-chan gave me is a pretty good color.
I walked a lot today, maybe I've lost 3 kilos.
I bought some gummy new today.
I feel good.
I'm not copying you.
You write like me.
You're Camon, right?
Cammon.
Don't worry if it rains.
I have an umbrella.
Today...
Mmm-hmm.
How far did I go?
Today... my hair was in bad shape because of the rain, but when I came here, it was silky smooth!
I got to read the manga I wanted to read!
Everyone who sees me says I'm cute!
I can eat strawberries when I get home!
See you later!
I even changed my new gummies.
It wasn't new earlier.
It's a new one this time!
We're going live this weekend!
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy right now!
My arms feel a little longer. Happy!
All the happiness in the world is coming to me!
Oh, wait! I'm so cute! Happy!
People are coming to see the showroom today. I'm so happy!
I'm the happiest person in the world!
The camera is off.
I was too happy.
I was happy.
When I'm happy, I'm happy.
Happy! That's nice. I was really happy to feel positive today.
That's great. I'm sure everyone is happy.
I'm sure everyone is happy. I'm sure this will make you happy, too.
Let's become a group like this.
Let's become a group like this, where everyone is happy.
Last!
Announcement of the happy points of the spring tour!
I'm going to announce what I thought was the happy points of the spring tour so far. Be careful not to spoil anything.
Here are the things that made me happy.
What is it? Happy things?
Happy things.
But this tour, did we think about the contents?
Yes, we are.
We have received many compliments on the contents and the set list,
We are quite happy.
I'm glad we used happy.
Yes, I'm happy. Happy.
The costumes are like Cinderella.
Like a shrake.
The word "cute" in the word "flower" is so cute.
I'm really happy about that.
Also, you've become more regressive with your voice.
Yes, I do.
Also, don't you want to have fun on this tour?
Yes, for sure.
Did you eat?
Yes, we did.
I'm eating a lot of food.
He eats a lot.
It's good food, so he eats delicious food that can only be found there.
I feel like I'm getting a lot of local food.
I'm glad.
It's gorgeous.
I also eat sweets once.
That's right.
Osaka Rubber became the background music for the guests.
Oh, that's right! I knew it.
Ai's wish came true.
In response to her passionate request.
Osaka Rubber Orgolu version.
I didn't think there was an Orgolu version.
I was like, "What's that?
I didn't know it existed.
What do you think?
I'm worried.
It's true that it was my first time to do the voice.
It was the first time for me to do it.
But I heard that there was such a call for this song.
Oh, you want me to hold it before you hold it?
Yes, yes, yes.
But I wanted to listen to it for a long time, and I had the feeling that everyone was really impressed with it,
So I wondered what it would be like.
So I wondered what it would be like, and here it is.
Yes, it was.
It changes every day.
It changed every day.
And the power of the people at that time was amazing.
It was amazing.
It's amazing, too.
It's hard to remember.
It's true, isn't it?
It created too much popularity.
Everyone is.
They came suddenly and were able to do that.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I think it's amazing.
I'm really looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm pretty good with the "Sole-kyu" level.
Sole level, yes.
If I didn't have a three-dimensional song, or a lead version, or something where they didn't call me by name..,
What? I would have been like, "What?
That's true.
It's been quite a while.
I guess the cola makes the audience feel more excited,
It makes me happy.
There were also some satsumas, weren't there?
I see.
What about the regional performances?
Shinagawa is not this time, though,
Yes.
Isn't it rare to see New Fiction or Satsuka with various songs?
Zooming in and out.
Yes, she's very cute.
Very cute.
You want to go that way?
Yes, yes.
I was zooming around like that.
Some people posted it on Twitter, and some people posted it on YouTube,
Some of them also put them on YouTube,
Please take a look at the songs of each performance.
Please do so.
I was very happy to be invited to Finale.
Thank you.
Icon is cute.
Icons are cute.
It's true.
I was happy to see the new fiction.
I know, right?
What did we look like when we were doing it?
I'm tempted to laugh if I'm not being polite,
I don't know what New Fiction is,
It was difficult.
That was pretty difficult.
Difficult points.
Point 1.
Also, Kozumi and the pictures looked difficult.
Indeed.
They all looked like this,
I'm like this, camera.I'm like this, camera.
I want to dance,
I want to dance.
I want to perform.
I thought it would be difficult.
That's for sure.
Yes, it is.
Spice it up here.
It feels like a live performance, doesn't it?
When we didn't have anything, it was normal.
I didn't think anything of it.
I didn't do it for about two or three years.
But the color of the live show was completely different when I was vocal and when I wasn't. It was the same live show, but I was enjoying it differently.
It was the same live performance, but there was a different way to enjoy it.
That's right.
Enjoy both.
It makes me happy.
I guess it's big.
So, this year's Halo! I'll be sure to announce the final day of the event as well,
I'll be sure to announce the final day as well.
We are looking forward to seeing you there.
I'm looking forward to seeing you.
May I go to the ending now?
Yes.
This is the ending of the 80th episode of Ukka no Yukarifuna Shonen Yumugen.
How was it?
It was fun. We even got to go cherry blossom viewing with the three of us.
Indeed.
We couldn't do that. In real life, right?
That's right.
That's why I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
So, let's announce it.
Wow, look.
The line is drawn so much, isn't it?
Yes, it is. I would like to announce the spring tour once again.
The Uka Spring Tour will end on April 16th at Shinagawa Stellar Ball in Tokyo.
Yay! That was quick.
Yes, we have toured 5 venues, and this will be the 6th show,
We are going to perform at a place with a fairly large capacity, so I hope many more people will come,
We are hoping that many more people will come,
I hope that you will invite your friends and family to come and enjoy the show.
And, this spring tour, Uka's one-man live show, is for newcomers,
We are giving away one two-shot ticket to newcomers.
And the members have come up with a setlist.
We will give away all 2 pieces to those who come to 6 cities.
You saw this the other day, right? Did you see it?
I saw it.
Isn't this amazing?
I think it's going to go pretty, pretty well.
Oh! What?
That's what it looks like.
Please look forward to it.
Also, on April 22, I will be performing at Idol Generation.
At Nakano Sunplaza at 1:00 p.m., isn't it?
The time to start?
The time to start is 1:00 pm.
And the next day, April 23rd, I will be performing at Clowfest 2023.
It's at the Sea Forest Water Stadium.
Our April turnout will be at 5:20pm.
This is the Diamond Stage.
Please join us for these two days.
Please do.
I'm looking forward to it.
Since I'm Se-chan, I'll be here for two days, please.
It's me and Ruri's birthday.
It will be at Studio Freedom Shibuya on June 3.
The first part is me, Yukirina's birthday show live at 2:00 p.m. I will play Toyz.
The second part will be me, happy Ruri Aoi, from 2:30 pm, and there will be a big traffic jam of cuteness.
Yes, I'll be there.
The FC selection process ends tomorrow,
Please don't forget about it.
Have you made progress yet? Preparations?
Yes, we are. They are going.
Have you decided?
It's decided.
So fast.
Too soon?
Isn't it early?
It's in April, right?
Yes, it is.
It was decided in June.
About a month and a half to go.
Did we decide that early?
It wasn't until April.
It was by April.
It was supposed to be by the end of March.
Then I'd better get ready too.
There may be some.
First of all, we have two birthdays coming up, so please do us a favor.
Please do.
So here are the final rankings.
Fifth place.
First place, Tanori Ranryujima. Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Shimarue-san. Thank you very much.
Third place, Babble Time no Hito. Thank you very much.
Second place, Sora-san. Thank you very much.
First place, Risaku. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your cooperation today.
The next broadcast will be on Wednesday, April 26th at 7:00 pm.
To make sure you don't miss this delivery, please register your favorite by pressing the heart mark.
We also have a private distribution, so please tune in there often as well.
Well, I guess I'm done.
Do you have any reflections?
Reflections on today?
Not at all anymore.
I am happy.
I don't want to think about negative things today.
It's a happy delivery.
Happy.
So, there was none. Today.
We had a good time, didn't we?
Impressions. How did everyone feel today?
Did you feel happy?
Happy?
Did I make you happy?
I'm going to visit the showroom soon.
Oh! Clear delivery.
Clear delivery. I'll let you know on Twitter.
Let's go through it. All together.
Yay for happy!
Yay!
I'm ChocoPonzu.
I love this Ponzu.
Yay!
I'm happy.
I'm going to have a good dream.
That's good. It is.
Happy.
It was fun.
Everybody's happy. That was good.
You're happy.
It's so meaningful.
Everyone is happy.
All I can say is happy.
Happy.
Like, happy.
It's good. If everyone is happy, you know.
That's happiness on our side.
That's right. I'm done.
Let's be happy.
Yes. That brings us to the end of the 180th edition of Uka-no-Yukari Couple's Showroom.
The next installment will be on April 26th, so please come and join us.
Please do.
That's all for now.
Happy.Happy.